const loadQuestions = () => {

    return [
        {
            question: "What is my middle name?",
            answers: [
                "Mitchell",
                "Mason",
                "Maxwell",
                "Michael"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Michael"
        },
        {
            question: "Where am I from?",
            answers: [
                "Florida",
                "Tennessee",
                "New York",
                "Illinois"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Tennessee"
        },
        {
            question: "What is my favorite cuisine?",
            answers: [
                "American",
                "Italian",
                "Chinese",
                "Japanese"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Japanese"
        },
        {
            question: "In a past life, I was a professional musician. What instrument did I play?",
            answers: [
                "Guitar",
                "Piano",
                "Drum Kit",
                "Didgeridoo"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Drum Kit"
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these artists is NOT a favorite of mine?",
            answers: [
                "Queen",
                "Billy Joel",
                "Journey",
                "Daft Punk"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Journey"
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these TV shows is NOT a favorite of mine?",
            answers: [
                "Scrubs",
                "Friends",
                "ER",
                "Top Gear"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "ER"
        },
        {
            question: "Which of these movies is NOT a favorite of mine?",
            answers: [
                "Emperor's New Groove",
                "Goldeneye",
                "The Holiday",
                "Saw"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Saw"
        },
        {
            question: "What foreign country have I visited?",
            answers: [
                "China",
                "Italy",
                "Japan",
                "Mexico"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "China"
        },
        {
            question: "What is my energy drink of choice?",
            answers: [
                "Red Bull",
                "Monster",
                "Nos",
                "Bang"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Red Bull"
        },
        {
            question: "What is my favorite Yankee Candle scent?",
            answers: [
                "Autumn Leaves",
                "Macintosh",
                "Clean Cotton",
                "Eucalyptus"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Clean Cotton"
        },
        {
            question: "What is my guilty pleasure?",
            answers: [
                "Listening to N'Sync",
                "Watching Judge Judy",
                "Perusing TMZ",
                "Stalking social media"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Watching Judge Judy"
        },
        {
            question: "What did I want to be when I grew up?",
            answers: [
                "Astronaut",
                "Doctor",
                "Meteorologist",
                "Firefighter"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Meteorologist"
        },
        {
            question: "What is my favorite holiday?",
            answers: [
                "Thanksgiving",
                "Christmas",
                "Halloween",
                "4th of July"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Thanksgiving"
        },
        {
            question: "Which theme park was I previously employed at?",
            answers: [
                "Disney",
                "Seaworld",
                "Busch Gardens",
                "Universal Studios"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Busch Gardens"
        },
        {
            question: "Which bone have I broken?",
            answers: [
                "Wrist",
                "Collar bone",
                "Ankle",
                "Never broken a bone"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Never broken a bone"
        },
        {
            question: "What is my favorite Disney park?",
            answers: [
                "Epcot",
                "Magic Kingdom",
                "Animal Kingdom",
                "Hollywood Studios"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Epcot"
        },
        {
            question: "What is my current job title?",
            answers: [
                "Application Developer",
                "Senior Consultant",
                "Software Engineer",
                "Network Manager"
            ],
            correctAnswer: "Senior Consultant"
        }
    ]
};